{"allRoundData":[{"name":"Spanish Words","timeLimitInSeconds":20,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":10,"questions":[{"questionText":"What is the correct translation for \"I\" in Spanish?:","answers":[{"answerText":"yo","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"yu","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"i","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"yoi","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the correct translation for \"you\"(informal) in Spanish?:","answers":[{"answerText":"tu","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"tue","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the correct translation for \"he\" (formal) in Spanish:","answers":[{"answerText":"ey","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"el","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"What is the correct translation for \"she\" in Spanish?:","answers":[{"answerText":"ela","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"ell","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"ella","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"What is the correct translation for \"you\" in Spanish?:","answers":[{"answerText":"used","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"udste","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"usted","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"What is the correct translation for \"we\"(masculine) in Spanish?:","answers":[{"answerText":"nostrosos","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"nostros","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"nosotros","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"nostro","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the correct translation for \"we\"(feminine) in Spanish?:","answers":[{"answerText":"nostrass","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"nosotrasa","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"nosotra","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"nosotras","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"What is the correct translation for \"you all\" in Spanish?:","answers":[{"answerText":"ustedes","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"usted","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"us","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"usteeds","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the correct translation for \"they\"(masculine) in Spanish?:","answers":[{"answerText":"ello","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"ellos","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"elloss","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"el","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the correct translation for \"I leave behind\" in Spanish?:","answers":[{"answerText":"abando","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"abandamos","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"abandono","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"abandonan","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the correct translation for \"You leave behind\"(informal) in Spanish?:","answers":[{"answerText":"abandamos","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"abando","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"abandon","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"abandonas","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"What is the correct translation for \"he, she, you leave behind\"(formal) in Spanish?:","answers":[{"answerText":"abandonan","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"abandona","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"abanda","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"abandonana","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the correct translation for \"we leave behind\" in Spanish?:","answers":[{"answerText":"abandonam","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"abandonamos","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"abandonamo","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"abando","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the correct translation for \"you all leave behind\" in Spanish?:","answers":[{"answerText":"abandonan","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"abandon","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"abandona","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"abadonan","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the correct translation for \"they leave behind\" in Spanish?:","answers":[{"answerText":"abadonan","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"abandonna","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"abandona","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"abandonan","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"What is the correct translation for \"I encompass\" in Spanish?:","answers":[{"answerText":"abarco","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"abarca","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"aborco","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"aborca","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the correct translation for \"You encompass\"(informal) in Spanish?:","answers":[{"answerText":"abarcass","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"abarcas","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"What is the correct translation for \"he, she, you encompasses\"(formal) in Spanish?:","answers":[{"answerText":"abara","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"aborco","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"abarca","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"What is the correct translation for \"we\" in Spanish?:","answers":[{"answerText":"abarca","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"abarcamos","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"abarcamo","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the correct translation for \"you all encompass\" in Spanish?:","answers":[{"answerText":"abarcan","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"abarca","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"abarcano","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"abandonan","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the correct translation for \"they encompass\" in Spanish?:","answers":[{"answerText":"abarcan","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"abarcon","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"abarca","isCorrect":false}]}]}]}